新皮夹
Hey, new wallet?
时下流行的
It was time.
保险套图案的
The old condom ring in the leather
皮夹已经不流行了
just doesn't saygarbage was full
瑞秋  你把空纸盒放进冰箱里
Rachel, you just put an empty carton back in the fridge.
我知道  因为垃圾袋满了
I know, but the garbage was full.
你有倒过垃圾没
Have you ever taken out the trash?
我以为你喜欢倒垃圾的
Well, I thought you liked doing it.
-左边第三个门  -好的
-third door on the left. -right!
崔格先生
Hey, mr. treeger.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
对不起
I'm sorry.
放了一段时间  不过
It's a little old but....
不是  我才通好
You're clogging up the chute i just unclogged.
对不起  我不常来
I'm sorry. i don't come in here a lot.
当然  你是小公主
Of course not. you're a little princess.
爸爸  帮我买披萨
Daddy, buy me a pizza.
爸爸  帮我买糖果工厂
Daddy, buy me a candy factory.
爸爸  叫猫的演员帮我唱生日快乐歌
Daddy, make the cast of cats sing "happy birthday" to me.
你以为你可以来这里
You think you can come here...
搞得一团乱  反正都有人会收
...make a mess and a big man in coveralls will clean it up?
去找别人好了
Well, why don't think of someone else for a change?
对不起
Okay, i'm sorry.
天  这样也要哭
God, if you're going to cry about it!
崔格把你惹哭了
Whoa-whoa, Treeger made you cry?
是的  他说了一些很恶劣
Yes! And he said really mean things
又扭曲真实的话
that were only partly true.
我去教训他
I'll teach him a lesson.
乔伊  不要  我看还是算了
Joey, please don't do that.I think it's best that we just forget about it.
你说得倒容易  受伤的又不是你
That's easy for you to say, you weren't almost just killed.
够了  家里又不是没大人
All right that's it, school is in session!
天  这是健身中心卡
My God! Is this a gym card?
没错  我是会员
Oh yeah, gym member.
我尽量1周去四次
I try to go four times a week,
但已经一千两百次没去了
but I've missed the last 1200 times.
那你怎么不退出
So why don't you quit?
你以为我没试过
You don't think I've tried?
你以为我喜欢每个月户头被扣50元
You think i like having $50 a month taken from my account?
他们逼你大老远跑过去
They make you go all the way down there.
用各种课程和效果让你昏头
They use all these phrases and peppiness to confuse you.
然后还叫玛丽亚出来
And then they bring out maria.
-是谁  -玛丽亚
-who is maria? -oh, maria!
她令人无法抗拒
You can't say no to her.
她是穿紧身衣的会员独享优惠
She's like this lycra, spandex-covered, gym treat.
要我陪你去  握着你的手
Do you need me to go with you and hold your hand?
不需要
No!
你可以单枪匹马应付她
You're strong enough to face her?
不行  你得陪我去
Oh, no. you'll have to come.
崔比亚尼  等一下
Tribbiani. hold on.
我去拿通马桶的
I'll get the plunger.
你等一下  你把我朋友瑞秋气哭了
You hold on. you made my friend rachel cry.
马上去跟她道歉
So you'll go and apologize to her...
否则我就通知房东
...unless you want me to call the landlord.
你要说什么
And tell him what?
你没听过男人不该让女人流泪
Maybe you haven't heard of "not making girls cry."
那你可能没听过
Maybe you haven't heard of the little
1968年租屋安定法案
heard about the Rent Stabilization Act of 1968!
我还真没听过
I have actually not heard of that.
你朋友违反这个法案
Yeah, well your friends are in violation of it.
我一直很客气  但我不必受这种罪
I've been nice until now, but i don't need this grief.
我要告诉房东
I'm telling the landlord...
莫妮卡非法分租她奶奶的房子
...monica's illegally subletting her grandmother's place.
你朋友就得搬出去了
Your friends are out of here, pal.
别说一些我不懂的事
Why don't you tell me something i don't know?
谁能让我今天不用上班
Oh please, somebody tell me I don't have to go to work today!
怎么了
What's the matter?
今天第一个客人是个大帅哥
Oh, my first massage today is this incredibly gorgeous guy,
每次见到他  我就想
and every time I see him I just want
替他免费服务一下
to do things to him that I'm not allowed to charge for.
那你就做
So do them for free.
不行  公司禁止
Oh no, it is forbidden!
跟客人乱来会被波特太太开除
No-no, Mrs. Potter fires people for fooling around with clients.
而且也违背我的按摩师誓言
And it's against my oath as a masseuse.
-你还得发誓  -是我自己
-They make you take an oath? -no, i made myself take one.
不得与客人乱来
Yeah, no fooling around with clients
和有备无患
...and always be prepared.
其实那是童军守则
Yeah, that one's actually from the Boy Scouts,
不过也说得通
but it just makes good sense.
你怎么不把他转给别人
Why don't you just give him to somebody else?
我可以应付  我很专业
No, I can handle it. No, I'm a professional.
菲比  那是新脚链
Oh Pheebs, is that a new ankle bracelet?
你还去做脚趾甲
Wow! And you got a pedicure.
你的脚可都打扮过
Your feet are all dressed up.
因为他在按摩台上只能看得到你的脚
That's the only part he can see when he's on the table!
你要用脚勾引他
You're going to do some feet flirting!
我不知道你们在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那你干嘛戴脚趾环
How do you explain the toe ring?
今天是阿拉伯公主日  行吗  别管我
It's arabian princess day at work. leave me alone!
我的英雄  怎样
My hero! what happened?
我说谁也不准欺负我的姐妹
I I went down there and told him no one treats my friends like that.
他最好上楼来道歉  就这样
And he better apologize. see you!
等一下
Wait a minute.
他怎么说
What did he say?
他说他不要  因为你们两个住这里是违法的
He wouldn't apologize because you're living here illegally.
他说他要赶你们走  回见
Instead, he'll evict you. see you later!
-你害我们要被赶走  -就叫你不要去找他
-you got us evicted? -i told you not to go down there.
他把瑞秋气哭了
He made rachel cry!
瑞秋本来就爱哭
Rachel always cries!
才没有
That's not true!
你给我下去拍他的马屁
You go down there, and you suck up to him.
使出浑身解数
You suck like you've never sucked before!
好  我尽量
All right, i'll try.
要是没成功  你们就先来跟我们住
But if I can't, you can stay with Chandler and I until you get settled.
-快去  -好好
-go! -all right, all right.
我得先问问钱德勒  不过应该可以
I mean I'll have to check with him first, but I'll think he'll be cool with it.
记住刚才所说的  要坚定
Now remember what we talked about, you gotta be strong.
再来一次
One more time,
难道你不想拥有平坦的小腹和结实的胸肌
Don't you want a washboard stomach and rock-hard pecs?
不想  我喜欢啤酒肚和大咪咪
No, i want a flabby gut and saggy man-breasts.
很好
Good! That's good!
我要退出会员
I wanna quit the gym.
你要退出
You wanna quit?
我就是要退出会员
I wanna quit the gym.
那就不能享用全新的瑞典SPA
You do realize you won't have access to our new swedish spa?
我要退出会员
I wanna quit the gym.
好  请找会员服务部的戴维
Okay, Dave in the membership office, handles quitters.
抱歉  你是会员吗
Excuse me. are you a member?
我吗  不是
Me? No
抱歉  非会员止步
Sorry. members only.
我要退出会员
I wanna quit the gym.
放心  要坚定
It's okay man, be strong.
你有加入任何健身中心
So, are you a member of any gym.
我没有  也不会  别白费唇舌了
No! And I'm not gonna be, so you can save you little speech.
好  没问题
Okay, no problem.
你过来一下
Could you come here for a second?
你好  我是玛丽亚
Hi, I'm Maria.
你的脚很漂亮
Wow, you have really pretty feet.
这些鸡爪
These old things.
帮我捏一下臀部  快痛死了
Would you mind spending some time on my siadic area, it's been killing me today.
你是说
You mean....
臀部是指
By sciatic, you mean...
毛巾盖住部分
...the towel-covered portion?
好的  没问题
Sure, i can do that.
因为臀部的肌肉
Because the muscles in the sciatic area can get...
紧实有弹性
...real nice and tight.
瑞克  你这里怎么会不舒服
So tell me, rick, how did you injure the area?
我为绿色和平组织静坐抗议16小时
A 16-hour sit-in for greenpeace.
-你刚才咬我  -没有
-did you just bite me? -no!
-怎样  -求你别赶她们走  是我的错
-What? -Please don't kick the girls out. this was my fault.
那你要我把你们赶走
You want me to kick you guys out instead?
不行  那小鸡小鸭要住哪里
No you can't do that, where would the chick and the duck live?
你们还养宠物
You have pets!
没有  那是绰号
Noo-no-no, no, those are nicknames.
我是小鸡  钱德勒是小鸭
Yeah. I'm the chick and Chandler is the duck.
我还以为是反过来
Huh, I would've thought it was the other way around.
拜托  让她们留下来
Come on man, just-just let the girls stay,
你要我做什么都行
I'll do whatever you want.
真的  什么都行
Really? You'll do anything?
对  没错
Yeah-yeah, absolutely.
我知道你能做什么了
Yeah, I've got something you can do.
什么
What is it?
你能当我的舞伴
Can you be my dancing partner?
这该不是牢里的黑话
That's not prison lingo, is it?
他的舞伴
His dancing partner?
对  他们有一个管理员舞会叫管舞会
There's this superintendents' dance, "the super ball."
他想引起一个女管理员玛姬的关注
He wants to impress marge, this lady super he likes.
那怎么不找女生练
why doesn't he practice with a girl?
他不好意思
Well, he's too shy,
他觉得他还没资格跟女生跳
he doesn't thing he's good enough to dance with girls yet.
是的
Yeah, right.
他差点害我跳进那个垃圾槽里
He almost danced me right down that garbage chute.
别再念了  你又没事
Would you let it go already? you're fine.
你退出了
So did you quit?
差一点
I almost did.
但我不能丢下罗斯不管
Couldn't leave ross there without a spotter.
你加入会员了
Wait, now, so you joined the gym?
是很好笑  为什么
And that's funny, why?
我只是在想像你在健身和
I was just, you know, picturing you working out, and....
就这样
Well, that's it.
我们毁了
We're doomed.
我们下半辈子
They'll take $50 a month from our
每个月都会白白扣掉50元
accounts for the rest of our lives.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
你们可以真的去健身
You could actually go to the gym.
或者去银行
Or we could go to the bank...
取消户头  断了他们的财路
...close our accounts and cut them off at the source.
你太有才了
You're a genius.
那我们就不能当银行好兄弟了
Oh, man! but then, we won't be bank buddies.
现在又多了一个理由
Now there's two reasons.
记得我说的那个帅哥客人
You guys, remember that cute client i told you about?
我咬了他
I bit him.
-咬哪里  -屁屁
-where? -on the tushy.
这样就不违反你的誓约
And that's not against your oath?
我知道  对不起  但是一摸到他
I know, but the moment i touch him...
我就想抛开旧誓约
...i want to throw out my old
来一个非限制级的
and take a new, dirty one.
下次你再按摩的时候  就让自己分心
Well, next time your massaging him, you should try and distract yourself.
对  像我如果在做很兴奋的事
Like when i'm doing something exciting...
又不想太
...and i don't want to get too...
兴奋
...excited.
我就会想别的事  像三明治
I try to thing of other things like ah sandwiches,
棒球
...and baseball...
还有钱德勒
and ah Chandler!
-谢谢你  乔伊  -不  谢谢你
-thank you. -oh, no, thank you.
我来了  咱们速战速决
All right, I'm here, let's ahh, get this over with.
好
Okay, well...
跟着我的舞步
...just follow my lead.
不必先做点准备
Don't we need to do some kind of preparation first?
像是喝个烂醉
Like get really drunk?
来  抱着我
Come on. hey, just put your arms around me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系  如果我是玛姬
No, it's okay, but if I'm Marge,
我的胸会被撞到背后去
...my breasts are coming out my back.
算了  我根本不会跳舞
Ahh, forget it! I'll never be any good at this,
我妈说得对
My mom was right.
我只是穿了衣服的大猪公
I'm just a big potato with arms and legs and a head.
别这样  你不是猪公
Come on man, you're not a potato.
总之我不适合跳舞
I'm sure as hell a dancer,it's no use
玛姬不会看上我的
Marge will never go for me.
别这么说  你只是
Come on, treeger. don't say that.
只是需要练习
You just need more practice.
来  再试一次
Come on. let's try it again.
而且就算有问题  也八成在我身上
Plus, it was probably mostly my fault anyway.
我不太习惯跟一个
I'm not that comfortable dancing with a
舞练得怎样  有同志情谊了
So how goes the dancing? gay yet?
你们欠我一个人情
You guys owe me bigtime.
那是什么
What was that?
你刚才在跳舞
You just did a little dancy thing.
-我没有  -你有
-no, i didn't. -yes, you did.
-你跳了几步  -看来你玩的很快乐
-you did a little hop. -you are so enjoying this.
我没有
No, i'm not.
而且那不是跳  那叫滑走步
And it wasn't a hop. it was a pas de bourree.
你还知道术语
You know the words!
真的很投入
You are so into this!
也许有一点吧
Maybe i'm enjoying it a little.
我越跳越好
i'm getting prert, it's manly.
好可爱  乔伊小舞伶
This is so sweet. joey, our little twinkletoes.
这可不是什么娘娘腔的舞
Hey-hey, hold on, this isn't some kind of like girly dance.
这是一种运动  很阳刚的
It's like a sport, it's manly.
-来  秀几个阳刚的舞步  -好
-show me some "manly" moves. -all right.
我不会带舞
I don't know how to lead.
你好
Hello.
我们想把账户关闭
We'd like to close our accounts.
关闭账户  有什么问题
Close your accounts? is there a problem?
没有  我们只是想结掉
No, we'd just like to close them.
终止帐户由蓝伯小姐负责
Ms. lambert handles all our closures.
请你来一下
Would you come over here, please?
我是凯伦
Hi, i'm karen.
我要退出这家银行
I want to quit the bank!
棒球
Okay. baseball.
瑞克打棒球  滑上二垒
Rick playing baseball. he slides into second.
也许裤子可以拉低一点
Maybe even his pants come down a little.
好  三明治
Okay, sandwiches. sandwiches.
三明治在盘子上
Okay, on a plate.
瑞克的裤子拉低一点
Maybe rick's pants come down a little.
钱德勒
Chandler.
钱德勒  有用
Okay, chandler. that's working!
钱德勒的膝盖
Chandler's knees.
钱德勒的脚踝
Chandler's ankles.
钱德勒的脚踝毛
Chandler's ankle hair.
完了
Oh, no!
好了
Okay, you're all set.
真是不可思议
Wow! that was amazing!
真的只有1小时
Was that really just an hour?
在1小时超长的世界里
In really long-hour world.
什么
What?
我很喜欢你
I have an enormous crush on you.
但你是客人  就算对你有感觉
But since you're a client, i can't ask you out...
我也不能约你
...even though you give me the feelings.
我完全不知道
I had no idea.
不过我可以找别的按摩师
I can always find another masseuse.
真的
Really?
Yeah, really.
怎么了
What?
我突然意识到我光着身体
Suddenly i'm very aware i'm naked.
好  别吵
Quiet down.
赛门先生等了天哪
Mr. simon's been waiting oh, my god!
我为什么没有
Why wasn't i offered that?
我愿意多付钱
I'd definitely pay more for that.
菲比  我们这里是有规矩的
We have rules here. this is not that kind of place.
我知道  但是你误会了
I know, but this isn't how it looks at all...
因为瑞克是我的丈夫
...because rick is my husband.
是吗
Oh, really?
你最好告诉他的另一个老婆
You'd better tell his other wife.
她已经打三次来查勤了
She called three times asking where he is.
好  我会告诉她
Yes, i will tell her.
你们没有结掉户头
So you didn't leave the bank?
没有  而且还一起办了个活存帐户
And somehow we ended up with a joint checking account.
你们要那个帐户做什么用
What will you ever use that for?
转帐给健身中心
To pay for the gym.
我今天过得真好
So i had a great day.
瑞克和我一拍即合  我们亲热
Rick and i hit it off. we were making out.
然后老板走进来  因为我卖春而开除我
Then my boss walked in and fired me for being a whore.
-你被炒鱿鱼  -天啊
-you got fired? -oh, my gosh!
感觉好怪  我从来没被开除过
It's so weird. i have never been fired from anything.
亲爱的
Sweetie.
我开始漫无目的的乱晃
I started walking around, not knowing what to do next.
还问路上的人
I started asking people on the
要不要按摩
street if they wanted massages.
结果警察也以为我是妓女
Then these policemen thought i was a whore too.
以一个妓女来说今天还真背
It's really been a bad day, whore-wise.
小鸭  小鸡在否
Hey, duck. is chick here?
在  兔宝宝
Yeah, bunny rabbit.
要练最后一支舞了
Ready for our last practice?
转圈还不够好
We're not getting that spin right
我房间太小了
because my apartment's too small.
-你要来这边练习吗  -我有别的想法
-want to use our place? -no, i had another idea.
成功了
We did it!
我知道  太棒了
I know, we did it!! Hey, that was incredible, huh?!
太精彩了  非常完美
That was amazing! we totally nailed it!
崔比亚尼  真是谢了
Hey, listen. thanks a lot, tribbiani.
糟糕  都几点了
Oh, my god! look at the time.
我得赶公车去舞会
I got to catch the bus to the ball.
祝你好运
Good luck.
还是你想练狐步舞  或是探戈
Unless you wanna practice the Foxtrot again? Or-or the Tango?
谢谢  不用了
Thanks, but no.
我已经可以跟女生跳了
You see, i think i'm ready to dance with girls.
-去迷倒她们  -好
-go get them, treeger. -right.
你想去吗  玛姬会带个朋友
Hey, ahh, you wanna come? Marge has a girlfriend.
真的
Really?
你会很习惯  她跟我差不多壮
You'd dance good with her. she's the same size as me.
不用了
No, i'm good.
看来你很有经验
It looks like you've got great experience.
我看看  你为什么辞去上一份工作
Let's see. reason for leaving last job?
他们以为我是妓女
They thought i was a whore.
好  有消息我们会通知你
Okay. we'll give you a call if anything comes up.
太好了  谢谢你
Great! Thank you very much.